姑娘们  准备好变得比你们现在更落伍吧
Girls, prepare to be more obsolete than you already are.
虽然这难度超级大
Which will be hard.
毕竟你们也就比报纸强一点点
You're one step above newspapers.
睁大狗眼看好未来啦
Behold, the future!
不是吧  未来的我还困在这里吗
Oh, no. I'm still here in the future?
阿憨  你的妹妹来了
Or, Han, your sister's here.
你好  你好[西语]  你好[日语]
Hello, hola, konichiwa.
我想现在是个坦白的好时机
I guess now's a good time to admit
我吃了一堆致幻蘑菇  我现在能看见
that I ate a bunch of shrooms and I'm seeing
一个别着领结的机器人
a robot in a bowtie.
这是个可以送餐的客房服务机器人
This is a room service robot that delivers food.
我阿姨的假日酒店倒闭了
My aunt's Holiday Inn went belly-up.
我拿到了这个跟床头柜[一夜情]
I got this and one night stand.
这会是你这辈子唯一拥有的一夜情吧
That's the only one night stand you're ever gonna get.
跟我在别家酒店的客房服务不一样啊
Must be a different kind of room service
在"它撸顿"钟点汽车旅馆
than they have at Tuggington's Hourly Motel.
第一撸免费呢
Where the first tug is free.
R2机器人  太好了
R2, thank God.
我还以为死星爆炸把你也炸没了呢
I thought I lost you when we blew up the Death Star.
您想要延迟退房吗
Would you like a late check out?
抱歉  兄弟  小女子多年前已去世[退房]
Sorry, toots. I checked out years ago.
列出晚餐特餐
List diner specials.
您点播了四部成人电影
You have ordered four adult films.
你撒谎
That's a lie.
我只点了三部
I've only ordered three.
关闭  机器人
Shut down, robot.
果然免费没好货  机器人也不例外
This is what happens when you get a robot for free!
R2机器人  别啊
R2, no!
尤达大师是我们的朋友啊
Yoda's our friend!
谁来救救我啊
Somebody help me!
如果那个机器人也会露乳沟跟偷银餐具
If that thing could show cleavage and steal silver wear,
那我就铁定要失业啦
I'd be out of a job.
我也等不及我们的约会了  鲍比
I can't wait for our date either, Bobby.
好  我们明天见
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
你先挂
You hang up first.
不要  你先挂...  他真挂了
No, you hang up-- Oh, he hung up.
我越来越喜欢这大兄弟了
I'm liking this guy more and more.
对啊  鲍比是不是超可爱
I know. Isn't Bobby the cutest?
没到抽烟的亚洲小孩那么可爱  但也不赖
Not smoking Chinese baby cute, but not bad.
麦克斯  我好激动啊
Max, I'm so excited.
我上一次去浪漫约会的时候
This is the first date I'll be going on
茱莉亚·罗伯茨还能担当浪漫喜剧主演呢
since Julia Roberts could still open a romantic comedy.
我还在气他们
I'm still pissed at them
偷走我的人生故事去拍《风月俏佳人》
for stealing my life story for "Pretty Woman."
片子里的坏律师简直是我的翻版
Jason Alexander's character was totally me.
我们的约会  他打算带我
For our date, he's thinking of taking me
去公园里来个午后野餐
on an afternoon picnic in the park.
去漂亮的那个
The pretty one,
有默剧演员被你揍蛋蛋后掉入水池的公园
where you crotch punched that mime into a pond.
你知道鲍比带你去白天约会
You know the fact that Bobby's taking you on a day date
是不好的征兆吧
is a bad sign, right?
很可能是因为他结婚了
It probably means he's married.
或更惨的  他怕黑
Or worse, afraid of the dark.
其实白天约会是我的主意
Actually, the day date was my idea.
你知道我们俩没结婚  对吧
You know we're not married, right?
我叫你老婆  是指老婆婆
That's not why I call you my old lady.
因为你会写给别人感谢函
It's cause you write thank you notes
还会用"哎哟喂"这词
and use the word jeepers.
哎哟喂  麦克斯
Jeepers, Max!
我是想到如果我晚上出去
I just figured if I go out at night,
你就得自己一个人照看甜品酒吧
you'll have to run the dessert bar alone
而你还没有独立看过店
and you've never done that before.
我也从来没有用牙线清理我后牙
I've also never flossed my back teeth.
不刮大风的时候  它们也都还好好的啊
And they're fine when it's not windy.
我能搞定
I got this.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我本来想着去散散步  伸展一下膝盖
I just thought I'd take a walk and stretch my knees.
然后想起来  我膝盖早没啦
Then I remembered I don't have any.
厄尔  我要像个正常人类  晚上去约会啦
Earl, I'm going on a night date, like a person.
麦克斯将会独自照看甜品酒吧  没问题的吧
Max will be running the dessert bar and that'll be fine, right?
说到大灾难  我就想起来
Ooh, speaking of disasters, that reminds me,
我得去百事达还一部灾难级烂片
I have to return "Risky Business" to Blockbuster.
百事达影带出租店什么时候关门
When do they close?
2009年就全关了
2009.
那我还有时间去还
So I still have time.
大伙快看  是土拨鼠
Hey, guys, look. It's a groundhog.
看来今年春季会来得早
So it's gonna be an early spring.
错了  他今年看到自己影子了
No. He saw his shadow this year.
长点知识再吐槽
Know your facts.
厄尔  你现在应该在餐厅里才对
Earl, you're supposed to be in the diner.
我还得叫我们的供虾商帮你代个班
I had to ask our shrimp supplier to cover for you.
我还以为你老妈才是我们的供虾商
I thought your mother was our shrimp supplier.
阿憨  我要像个正常人类  晚上去约会啦
Han, I'm going on a night date, like a person.
麦克斯将会独自照看甜品酒吧  没问题的吧
Max'll be running the dessert bar and that'll be fine, right?
当然啦  就像我上次让她帮我照看餐厅一样
Sure, like when I had her run the diner by herself.
这事从来没发生过  因为我又不是傻逼
Which never happened because I'm not a damn fool!
咱们走  厄尔
Let's go, Earl.
好吧  行
All right, fine.
反正我的膝盖也留在那里了
I left my knees there, anyway.
我...  我刚好在这附近
Hey, I was, uh-- I was just in the neighborhood
所以我就决定倒两班地铁再骑公共自行车
and thought I'd hop on two subways and a Citi Bike
来跟你打个招呼
and come say hi.
城市公共自行车吗
A Citi Bike?
我这个城市女孩受宠若惊啊
Oh, this city gal is flattered.
"哎哟喂"
Jeepers.
他是不是天下第一可爱
Isn't he the cutest?
没有狗狗睡觉时在跑步那么可爱  但也还行啦
Oh, not dog running in his sleep cute, but I'm all right.
鲍比  我有个好消息
Bobby, I have some good news.
我不想你觉得我好上  骚货
I don't want you to think I'm loose or fast
或这年头孩子用的其他词
or whatever the kids say,
但我有空像个正常人类一般晚上去约会了
but I am available for a night date, like a person.
真的吗  太好啦
Hey, really? That's great.
我通常都把我的白天约会留给我奶奶
I usually save my day dates for my grandma.
她喜欢中午吃晚饭
She likes a noon dinner.
-我喜欢中午...  -你闭嘴
- I like a noon-- - No.
既然我们是要晚上约会
Since we're going out at night,
我就可以取消本来要做的浪漫差事
I can cancel all the romantic errands
比如一起去银行办事啊
we were gonna run to the bank
或是一起去领我干洗的衣服
and my dry cleaners.
现在我可以带你去看场电影
Now I can take you to a movie.
有一家新的电影院有沙发跟服务员
There's this new theater that has couches and waiter service.
我们在餐厅里打工
Wow. We work in a restaurant
可我们餐厅都没有服务员呢
and we don't have waiter service.
他居然有银行账户跟干净衣服吗
He has a bank and clean clothes?
卡洛琳  可别毁了这桩好姻缘
Caroline, don't screw this up.
呼叫品客博士  我的肚子需要你
Paging Dr. Pringle, you're needed in my stomach.
运作甜品酒吧的小测试题
Okay, pop quiz on running the dessert bar.
当有顾客噎住了  你该怎么处理
What do you do if a customer chokes?
相信我  有需要我给某人喉咙割开个洞时
Look, if I have to cut a hole in someone's throat,
我就会给那人喉咙割开个洞
I'll cut a hole in someone's throat.
你不能什么问题都在人家身上割个洞解决啊
Cutting a hole in people can't be your answer for everything.
下一题  如果发生火灾应该怎么办
Next one. What do you do if there's a fire?
细节追问
Follow up question:
火是我放的  还是别人放的
did I or did I not start said fire?
这两种情况我都会在某人身上割个洞
Either way, I'm cutting a hole in someone.
这场测验你不及格两次了
Okay you failed this quiz now twice.
尤其是作文的部分
Especially the essay portion.
我要打给鲍比取消约会
I'm calling Bobby and canceling.
她们在家
They're home.
他的意思是  你们好啊
He means, hey, girls.
你们为什么会有我们公寓的钥匙
How did you get a key to our apartment?
上面明确写了
They specifically say on them,
"不许给奥列格配备份"
"Do not copy for Oleg."
我发现你不穿裤子进家居连锁店
I find that when you go in a Home Depot pantless,
他们会满足你一切愿望  只求送你走
they'll do anything to get you out quick.
我们在约会之夜时会来你们这里
We come down here on our date nights
假装我们是俩穷鬼姑娘
to pretend we're two destitute girls
为了取暖而睡在一起
who are sleeping together for warmth.
你们为什么要来我们家搞
Why do you guys come here?
你们为什么不能去自助餐餐厅之类的地方搞
Why don't you go to, like, I don't know, Olive Garden?
对啊  这是约会之夜
Yeah, this is date night.
不是找个死胖子拍我们做爱之夜
Not find an overweight guy to film us night.
宅在家是一种传统
Staying in is a tradition.
在波兰  我们不太能出门
You know, in Poland, you really can't go outside
因为外面有野生猛犬
because of all the wild dogs.
要不是因为我们养的狼
And if it wasn't for the wolves,
我们真是哪也去不了
You wouldn't be able to walk anywhere.
当然啦  你还是得带着你的赶秃鹰棍
Of course, you still need your vulture stick.
说到秃鹰虎视眈眈绕着死尸转
Speaking of vultures circling a dead body,
卡洛琳今晚有约会呢
Caroline's got a date tonight.
天啊  麦克斯  你想笑死我啊
Oh, my God, Max. That's a good one.
再说一次这笑话
Say it again.
不是  这不是笑话
No, it's not a joke.
我真的要去约会了
I'm really going on a date.
别说了  真要命  我得去尿尿了
Stop it! Oh, my gosh, I'm gonna pee.
我要去那个有沙发的新电影院
I'm going to that new movie theater with couches.
简直就像在自己家里  除了沙发底下
It's like watching at home, but there isn't a giant spring
不会有大弹簧顶着你屁股
poking you in the butt.
你表现得好  就会有人顶
Play your cards right, there will be.
给  两杯甜鸦酒
Here you go. Two Liquor Doodles.
说到"舔"她的"鸟"...
And speaking of licking her doodle...
闭嘴
No.
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
我不是把你留在家里了吗
I thought I left you at the apartment.
当年绑架我的人
Which is what my abductor said
在冰激凌店遇到我时也这么说
when I ran into him at Baskin-Robbins.
等等  他是在那里工作  还是你想吃冰激凌了
Wait, did he work there or did you just want ice cream?
因为如果他是在那里工作  你为啥还去...
Because if he worked there, why would you go...
反正今晚我让鲍比来店里接我
Anyway, I'm having Bobby pick me up here
这样我才能一直手握灭火器
so I can keep my hand on the fire extinguisher
直到我不得不跟他开始我们的约会
until we get to our wherever it is he's taking me.
不是  你就是不相信我
No. You don't trust me.
你觉得我会毁了我们的店
You think I'm gonna mess this place up.
卡洛琳走了没
Ah, Caroline gone yet?
因为我给咱们弄来了高档大麻...
'Cause I got us some high-grade pot...
好立刻上交给相关单位
to turn into the authorities immediately.
厄尔  你玩消失的频率比烟枪女星
Earl, you go AWOL more often than Mischa Barton
跑离片场抽烟还频繁
on a movie set.
我该怎么做才能把你留在餐厅
What do I have to do to keep you in that diner?
让我跟哈利·贝瑞约会就不错
Well a date with Halle Berry would be nice.
薪水能达到法定最低工资也不错
I also wouldn't hate minimum wage.
给你一个奶油糖布丁如何
How about a butterscotch pudding?
这个也行
That works, too.
那个布丁这些年来救过我无数次
That pudding has saved me thousands over the years.
还有是谁告诉他有法定最低工资这件事
And who told him about minimum wage?
你就去约你的会  可以吗
Will you just go on your date already?
-艾希莉  -阿什莉
- Ashley! - Ashleigh!
天啊  天啊  天啊  天啊  天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
天啊  姐妹会的妞
Oh, my God. Sorority sisters?
麦克斯  你讨厌死她们了
Max, you hate them.
我就曾经在姐妹会里待过
I mean, I was a sorority sister.
你看起来好漂漂啊
You look so good!
闭嘴  我胖了足足两斤呢
Shut up, I gained, like, two pounds.
你才闭嘴  你看起来都快瘦死了
Oh, you shut up. You look like you're dying.
放轻松  我会处理好她们
Just relax, I'll take care of them.
我说的处理不是打给我那个
And I don't mean calling my friend Dmitri,
有自己的大型垃圾桶的好友德米特里
who has his own dumpster.
姐妹花的妞们
Oh, sorority sisters, huh?
EΦ姐妹会  我们已经没看到彼此
Epsilon Phis! And we haven't seen each other
足足要三天了呢
in, like, three days.
很明显就能看出来啊
Uh, that's pretty obvious.
我去给你们拿菜单
Let me get you some menus.
你看  没人受伤
Eh? Nobody got hurt.
你的眼睛不那么抽抽  我心里会好受许多
I'd feel better if your eye wasn't twitching like that.
卡洛琳  你今天美呆了
Wow, Caroline, you look beautiful.
说到漂亮  这么赞的店谁装修的啊
Speaking of beautiful, who built this awesome place?
一男的  我今晚要跟他去约会
This guy. I'm going out with him tonight.
而且他超可爱呢
He's cute, too.
够啦  我知道你是在说我  但我要吃醋了
Okay, I know you're talking about me, but I get jealous.
我要跟你们说我当年总交代我妈的话
I'm gonna tell you what I always told my mom:
出去野吧  喝个大醉  而且记得事后避孕药
go out, get plastered and you don't have to wait
不用等到事后的早上才吃
till the morning after to take the pill.
那只是名字而已
That's just a name.
没事的  我在来的路上吃过了
It's okay, I took mine on the way over.
玩得开心  麦克斯  不许玩得开心  再见
Have fun Max. Do not have fun. Bye!
老娘能搞定几个姐妹会的妞
I can handle a few sorority girls.
先检查一下我还有没有德米特里的电话
Let me make sure I still have Dmitri's number.
邦妮
Bunny!
艾希莉  阿什莉
Ashley! Ashleigh!
天啊  她们在倍增
God, they're multiplying.
你看起来好赞啊
Oh, you look so good!
-你闭嘴  -你才闭嘴
- Oh, shut up. - You shut up!
你们真的应该多听听彼此说话
You guys should really listen to each other.
电影院里有沙发吗
Couches in movie theaters?
我感觉自己好像凯特王妃啊
I feel like Kate Middleton right now.
我很庆幸你很容易满足
I'm glad you're easily impressed.
等情人节  我就带你去平价百货里的咖啡厅
For Valentine's Day, I'll take you to the Super Target cafe.
这种好消息我憋不住啊
Well I can't just sit on that kinda news.
我得立刻打给麦克斯跟她分享
Let me just call Max and tell her.
没接  直接进了她的放屁语音信箱
Nope, straight to her outgoing fart message.
晚上好  各位  我叫马歇尔
Bon soir, everybody. My name is Marcel,
我将是你们今晚电影体验的监护人
and I will be the curator for this evening's cinematic experience.
这部欧文·格雷伯曼都点赞的电影
The film, which Owen Gleiberman has hailed,
是库布里克式的力作
a Kubrickesque tour de force,
将以数字高清方式放映...
will be screening in DCP...
怎么了  这位影迷有什么问题吗
Uh, yes? A question from a fellow cinephile?
点薯条时  调味炸薯条是得单独点
Do I have to order the seasoned fries separate from the regular ones
还是可以和普通的混点
or can I just get them mixed?
单点多一块
It's a dollar extra.
我将会在电影开始后为各位点单
I'll be taking orders once the movie starts.
随便吧
Whatever.
薯条这问题问得好
Hey, great question about the fries.
我刚还想接着问能不能免费续杯
I had a follow up about free refills.
没事吧
Everything okay?
我在点评网上查这家影院
I was just, um, checking this place on Yelp.
顺便看看我们的甜品酒吧有没有上新闻
And to see if the dessert bar was on the news.
或是成为一片火海
Or engulfed in flames.
你也看见那根会跳舞的热狗啦
You saw the dancing hot dog.
它说不许玩手机
No cell phones.
你们俩怎么会在这里
What are you guys doing here?
我白用《嗜血法医》式防水布铺床了吗
Did I cover my bed in "Dexter" tarp for nothing?
我们在约会呢
We're on a date.
疯狂憋着不爱爱之夜
Trying like crazy not to have sex.
通常当影院的灯暗下
Usually, when the lights go down in the movie,
我的裤子会被拉下
so do my pants.
然后我人也会蹲下
And then, so do I.
当然我们通常得在大厅看到
And of course we would have to see a super sexy poster
史蒂夫·布西密的超性感海报才有性致
of Steve Buscemi in the lobby.
我是鲍比  很高兴认识你们
Hi, I'm Bobby. Nice to meet you.
抱歉  我比不上史蒂夫·布西密
Sorry, I'm no Steve Buscemi.
我高中时还是个牙套弟
I had braces in high school.
你们俩约会还带着芭芭拉吗
You guys brought Barbara on your date with you?
当然没带  她跟保姆在一起呢
Of course not. She's with the babysitter.
我们用婴儿车偷带晚餐进来
We used the carriage to sneak in our dinner.
拜托  我们才不会花高价吃影院的鸡
Hey, we're not gonna pay movie chicken prices.
奥列格  给我掰个鸡腿
Oleg, tear me off a leg.
很好
Good. Yeah.
那是警报声吗
Was that a siren?
是电影里传来的声音
Oh, it's coming from the screen.
这部电影就叫《警报声声》
The movie's called "Sirens."
我知道  但我觉得我听到的不止电影里的声音
I know, but I thought I heard another one under it
那个警报声听起来好像是奔着甜品酒吧去的
that sounded like it could be heading for a dessert bar.
你是不是玩得不开心
Are you not having a good time?
你不喜欢看电影吗
Do you not like movies?
拜托告诉我你不喜欢看戏剧
Please tell me you don't like plays.
不  我玩得很开心啊
No, I'm having a great time.
也拜托不要告诉我  你觉得音乐剧算戏剧
And please tell me you don't consider musicals plays.
我不想查麦克斯岗
Hey, I don't wanna check in on Max
因为她会觉得我不信任她
'cause she'll think I don't trust her.
要不你们帮我查麦克斯岗
So can you check in on Max?
因为我真的不信任她
Because I really don't trust her.
老娘在啃鸡腿呢
Uh, I got chicken hands!
你干嘛不让你男朋友代劳啊
Why don't you ask your boyfriend to do it?
首先我们还没确立关系呢
First, we haven't discussed labels yet.
其次  我不想让他觉得我玩得不开心
And second, I don't want him to think I'm not having fun.
我玩得太开心了
I'm having so much fun.
如果音乐剧对你很重要  我愿意陪你去看
I would go to a musical if it was important to you
我来问吧
I'll do it.
发信息  出去
Texting? Out.
在你学会尊重电影艺术前
And don't come back until you gain some respect
不许回来
for the art form.
谁点的辣味热狗上配玉米片
Who ordered the chili dog with the nachos on top?
或许这样对谁都好
Well it probably all for the best.
反正你们都要走了
Since you're leaving anyways,
你们可以亲自去看一下麦克斯
you can check in on Max in person.
行吧
I guess.
我们准备把你的床"搞得鸡飞狗跳"
Since we're about to chicken up your bed.
EΦ姐妹一辈子
Epsilon Phi until we die!
第一次就听清了  我在努力送你们到下辈子
Ah, heard you the first time. I'm working on it.
不是吧  艾希莉
Aw, come on, Ashley!
我还以为阿什莉才会这么怂呢
That's something I'd expect from Ashleigh.
能帮帮忙吗
Can you do something?
喂  她们想放个穷妹子进姐妹会哦
Hey you, uh, they're trying to let a poor girl in the sorority.
谁  长得丑吗
Who? Is she ugly?
好了  看见没
There you go. See?
她就跟五分钟前一样讨人厌
She's as annoying as she was five minutes ago.
你们想来点什么
Now what do you people want?
再多来几杯
Um, more shots.
还有阿什莉吐在艾希莉的包包里了
Also, Ashleigh threw up in Ashley's purse.
我从贩酒店回来了
Ah, back from the liquor store.
抱歉我去太久了
Sorry I took so long.
我当时不知道自己去的是家居店
I didn't realize I was at a Pottery Barn.
趁现在你脑袋糊涂
Well, while I've got you confused,
你现在重回岗位
How about you get back to work
帮我把这些喝的端给客人如何
and bring out these drinks for me?
我才没有糊涂
I am not confused.
我知道自己是这家星期五餐厅的女服务员好吗
I realized I'm a waitress at this TGIFridays.
祝贺我们吧
Congratulate us!
我们有整整两小时没做爱了
We've just gone two hours without having sex.
打破了我们之前差一点点就两小时的记录
Which breaks our old record by pretty close to two hours.
卡洛琳让我来看看你怎么样
You know, Caroline asked us to check up on you
因为她担心你
because she was worried.
我们本来不应该告诉你的
We're not supposed to tell you that.
但我的半只烤鸡不得不留在电影院里了
But I had to leave a half a roasted chicken in the movie theater.
所以老娘偏要说
So I am!
她都不知道今晚这帮姐妹会的妞
Does she have any idea what I've been through tonight
让我遭了什么罪
with these sorority girls?
她可能还觉得我清醒着呢
For all she knows, I'm sober.
姐妹会的妞
Sorority girls, huh?
我进过一次姐妹会
I was in a sorority once.
一直藏到被人发现
Until they found me.
为什么这么久
What's going on?
我们下一轮酒是要等一辈子吗
We've been waiting for our next round of drinks for, like, ever.
麦克斯
Wow, Max.
你真的要让电影《完美音调》里一样的婊气妹
Are you really gonna let the cast of "Pitch Perfect"
这么跟你说话吗
talk to you like that?
当老板的不会打姐妹会的妞
People in charge don't punch sorority girls.
我们能分开算账吗
And can we get separate checks?
真的不会吗
Or do they?
分开算账
Separate checks?
你觉得我像是算数学家吗
Do I look like a mathologist to you?
有问题吗
Is that a problem?
因为我可不想在点评网上写些评论
'Cause I'd hate to have to say something on Yelp.
点评网
Yelp?
卡洛琳查那个比上谷歌查自己还多
Caroline checks that more than she Googles herself.
完全没有问题
Uh, not a problem at all.
酒和分开算账
Drinks and separate checks...
不管那是啥  马上就来
whatever that is... coming right up!
谢谢  你最招人喜欢了
Thanks! You're the cutest.
不  你才是
No, you are.
貌似某人有大麻烦
Looks like someone's in the weeds
而且不是吸大麻的那种大麻烦
and not just smoking it for a change.
别光跪着  站起来端酒给客人
Don't just kneel there, bring these drinks out.
我十分钟内要学会所有数学
I have to learn all of math in ten minutes.
好吧  我留下来帮你
All right, I'll stay.
但只是因为我想让你体验风水轮流转
But only because I want you to see how it feels
老板忙死  员工不给力...
when the shoe is on the...
快他妈上酒
Serve the damn drinks!
她知道了
She gets it.
小姐妹  你在这家星期五餐厅工作多久了
How long you been working at this Fridays, sonny?
一切还好吗
Uh, is everything all right?
你都去了九次洗手间了
You've been to the bathroom nine times.
你是毒瘾犯了吗
Are you a drug addict?
还是沉迷玩糖果消消乐
"Candy Crush" Junkie?
我们可以一起想办法戒瘾
We can deal with it together.
抱歉  鲍比  但你知道乌龟能感应到
I'm sorry, Bobby, but you know how turtles can sense
它们的好朋友龟壳顶地  翻不过身来
if their turtle best friend is stuck upside down on its shell,
四脚朝天在空中乱晃的无助感吗
its turtle legs all wiggling in the air?
所以是毒瘾犯了
So it is drugs.
那就好  戒糖果消消乐太难了
Good. "Candy Crush" is tough.
我们帮我妈戒过这个毒
We went through that with my mom.
太困难了  我们差点把房子赔进去了
It's a killer. We almost lost our house.
不  我和麦克斯是乌龟
No, Max and I are the turtles.
我能感应到她在甜品酒吧忙不过来的无助感
And I can feel she's trapped on her back at the dessert bar.
好吧  我虽然不是很了解麦克斯
All right, look, I don't know Max that well.
但我现在又多了解你一点
But I've gotten to know you a little bit
你的肩膀上长了一颗
and you have a really good,
非常好非常漂亮的脑袋
really beautiful head on your shoulders.
你相信了她才来约会  就应该继续信任直觉
You trusted Max. You should trust your own instincts.
你说得对  我脑袋的形状的确不错
You're right. I do have a nice shaped head.
我不会再担心她可能会把酒吧烧掉了
And I'm gonna stop worrying that she might burn the bar down.
那就好  什么  真的假的
Good. What? Seriously?
那地方可是费了我不少心血呢
I put a ton of work into that place.
要不这样  这电影也不好看
You know what? This movie sucks.
我们出去吃点甜品吧
Let's get out of here and go get some dessert.
我知道一个很棒的地方
I know a great place.
你真是太贴心了
That is so sweet.
我之前还怕你觉得我疯了呢
And I was so worried you'd think I was crazy.
你就是个疯婆子[香蕉]
Oh, you're bananas.
但我就喜欢疯婆子
But I like bananas.
不是说那种水果  香蕉的口感让我觉得恶心
Not the fruit. The texture grosses me out.
是你
But you.
你这句话让我想亲你
I could kiss you for that.
你可以亲我啊
You know, you actually could.
你说得对  我可以
You're right, I can.
好了  我们真应该走了
Yeah, we should get out of here.
好了没  这比我一直毕不了业花的时间还久
Hello? It's taking longer than it took me to almost graduate.
你就跟你的接发再等一会儿吧
Just hang onto your hair extensions.
有这么明显吗
They're obvious?
我的乌龟感应灵验了
My turtle sense was right.
麦克斯四脚朝天  而且上面没有压着雄乌龟
Max is on her back and she's not under a boy turtle.
或许她没事呢  我没闻到糊味
Maybe she's all right. I don't smell fire
大家也都还四肢健全  安然无恙
and everyone's shoulders are still in their sockets.
为什么分开算账要算这么久啊
Why are separate checks taking so long?
麻烦找下钱好吗
Can we please get our change?
你把食物那部分钱都算邦妮账上了吧
Um, you put the apps on Bunny's bill, right?
因为大部分都是她吃的  向来如此
'Cause she ate the most, as per ush.
别再告诉别人我吃东西
Stop telling people I eat!
你也别再告诉别人我法学院入学考试的成绩
Stop telling people my LSAT scores.
不许讲话  现在我又得重新算过
Stop talking! Now I have to start over.
我现在脑子里一堆数字  而且个个火冒三丈
I have a lot of numbers in my head and they're all angry.
我得去帮她  分开算账难度太高
I have to help her. Separate checks?
麦克斯把13叫做"10  3"
Max calls 13 "Ten three."
卡洛琳  等等  让她试试自己处理
Caroline, wait. Let her try and handle this on her own.
否则我们永远没机会进行下一次约会
Otherwise, we'll never be able to go on a second date.
但她真的需要...
But she really nee...
我们还有下一次约会吗
There's gonna be a second date?
听好了  各位
Okay, listen up, everybody!
冷静
Calm down!
我们用这个来代替分开算账
Here's what we're gonna do instead of separate checks:
我不擅长数学  但10  3年来
I'm not good at math, but I have been
一直是一名出色的谈判专家
a negotiations expert for ten three years.
艾希莉  邦妮会从支付宝转给你6块
Ashley, you're gonna get $6 from Bunny's PayPal account
她还会帮你做指甲
and she's gonna do your nails.
邦妮  你用微信转安布尔20块
Bunny, you're gonna Venmo Amber $20
她会把基佬密友戴夫借给你
And she's gonna let you borrow her gay friend Dave
领去参加姐姐婚礼
for your sister's wed.
大家都没意见吧
Everybody good?
你们有10  3分钟做决定
You've got ten three minutes to decide.
没意见
We're good.
好了  问题解决
Okay, problem solved.
麦克斯  刚才真是太棒了
Max, that was amazing.
我就知道你能独当一面
I knew you could do that on your own.
屁咧  你一直在监视我
No you didn't, you were spying on me.
是她的乌龟感应触发了
Her turtle sense went off.
你都不需要我了  我有点小难过会不会很奇怪
Is it strange that I'm a little sad that you don't need me?
我没说我不需要你
I didn't say I don't need you,
但你的确有点小悲哀[难过]
but you are a little sad.
厄尔  很高兴能跟你一起当服务员
Earl, it was a pleasure waiting tables at your side.
我们之间擦出的火花无法用科学诠释
You and I have a chemistry you can't make in a lab.
你跟男人说话的方式真的很奇怪
You have a real strange way of talking to dudes.
不好意思
Uh, hi.
你们知道里面有两个光着身子的人
Did you guys know there are two naked people
在里面互啃对方身上的鸡肉吗
eating chicken off each other in there?
什么  那些水槽没有做防鸡层
What? I haven't chicken-proofed those sinks.
好了  我闭上眼睛要进去啦
All right, I'm closing my eyes and then I'm coming in.
他是不是很勇敢啊
Isn't he brave?
那他有没有勇敢地闯入前人所未至的领域
So did he bravely go where no man has gone before?
也就是你的毛衣里呢
Under your sweater?
没有  但我们在电影院里接吻了
No, but we were smooching in the movie.
闭嘴别说了
Shut up!
-不  你闭嘴听我说  -我是说真的
- No, you shut up. - No, really,
把你的嘴闭上  老娘累死了
shut your damn mouth, I'm exhausted.